{
    "id": "f9964830a74c4d6e900c0bc83c4da885",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is afraid to speak, lest he ………………………. be laughed at.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a25ac6b82c2473d973c662d69335e4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said he ………………………….  not come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b6963d726b34e94afed6eba401264ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Had I seen you, I ………………………. have come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "153ac549bbd443b0902ebfbacd9bb84c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… swim across the river when he was young.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d5b4b22ad84041dfa286c629b49af99b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me that he ………………………. not help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f79abe664edc4995b9079597be3efedf"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you live long!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "May",
                "Will",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46f9226fdca644d298ba5c4dcf27b58c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had studied medicine I ………………………. have become a doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "284d457ce158498f9126df39c496f01b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. have arrived in time, if I had not lost my way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14f78a72f91747e98318c1814aa34a92"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… very much like to see my old classmates.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec32d40589b3489bbf13342b99775074"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………. not hurry, we have  got plenty of time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d67d91c896d5462987ef6df9fceae514"
        }
    ]
}